Stand and sing for Zambia, proud and free,
Land of work and joy in unity,
Victors in the struggle for our rights,
We've won freedom's fight.
All one, Strong and Free.
Africa is our own motherland,
Fashion'd with and blessed by God's good hand,
Let us all her people join as one,
Brothers under the sun.
All one, Strong and Free.
One land and one nation is our cry,
Dignity and peace 'neath Zambia's sky,
Like our noble eagle in its flight,
Zambia, praise to thee.
All one, Strong and Free.
Praise be to God,
Praise be, praise be...
Praise be, praise be!
Bless our great nation,
Zambia, Zambia...
Zambia!
Free men we stand
Under the flag of our land.
Zambia, praise to thee!
All one, Strong and Free!